Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
- Box: 7, folder: 1 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Item 19: Booklet Answers Questions bout Our Industry, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    March 9. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: New Rate Increases Sought, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    August 21. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: New "Off-Hour" Identification Procedures Established For General Offices and Service Building, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    September 9. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Premiums For Basic Hospitalization Plan Going Up September 1, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    August 18. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: U.S. Department of Labor Bars Sex Discrimination On Government Contract Work, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    August 11. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: C&M Plant Clerks Vote Against Union, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    June 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Study Relocation Plans For Employes Affected By Construction of New Office Building, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    June 29. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Sale of Traffic Appliances To Customers Will Be Discontinued At Customer Offices, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    June 16. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Supervisors To Assist In U.S. Savings Bond Drive, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Item 28: Computer Area Security Improved--4th Floor Service Building, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    June 20. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Three Appointed To Proposal Plan Committee, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    September 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Facts About Fermi, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    September 4. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Torch Drive Dates Announced, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    September 29. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Organization Changes - Recently Announced, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    September 12. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: New "Copy Center" For General Offices, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    July 18. Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Employes Report Offensive MailHow To Stop It, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    July 15. Item is in English.
  - Item 35: Load Forecasting - Planning For The Future, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    July 31. Item is in English.
  - Item 36: Display Shop To Consolidate With Graphic Arts, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Item 37: School Bells To Ring Soon, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    August 7. Item is in English.
  - Item 38: Managing Cost Improvement The Search Goes on For New Ways to Reduce Expense, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    June 13. Item is in English.
  - Item 39: Organization Changes - Recently Announced, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    December 31. Item is in English.
  - Item 40: Vertical Management Team Building, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    January 27. Item is in English.
  - Item 41: The U.D.A. Common Utility Corridors Planning Project and The Work of the Task Force Assigned To It, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    February 16. Item is in English.
  - Item 42: Employe Services Coordinating Alcoholism Assistance Program, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Item 43: Management Reviews Action To Increase Minorities In Work Force, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    February 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 44: Wanted: J.A. Advisors, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    September 24. Item is in English.
  - Item 45: Rise In City Income Tax, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    September 25. Item is in English.
  - Item 46: Personal Benefits Report, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    April 7. Item is in English.
  - Item 47: "No Charge" Installations Scheduled, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    June 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 48: Any Way You Look At ItOur Safety Slip Is Showing, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    September 27. Item is in English.
  - Item 49: Unauthorized and Irregular Practices Corrected, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    February 8. Item is in English.
  - Item 50: Details Still Incomplete On Pumped-Storage Project, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    December 6. Item is in English.
  - Item 51: Detroit Edison Casualty In Vietnam, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    June 9. Item is in English.
  - Item 52: Election of Company Officers Announced At Board Meeting In New York, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    April 19. Item is in English.
  - Item 53: Facts On the PLC Discussions, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    March 20. Item is in English.
  - Item 54: Edison's Comfort Conditioning Carnival, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    February 15. Item is in English.
  - Item 55: Act Grads - It's Election Year, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    February 10. Item is in English.
  - Item 56: Rate Increase Petition Before M.P.S.C. On April 14, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    March 10. Item is in English.
  - Item 57: Testimony Presented At Hearings In Detroit and Lansing, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    April 21. Item is in English.
  - Item 58: Protecting People and Property, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    April 14. Item is in English.
  - Item 59: G.O. Area Security Strengthened, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    April 22. Item is in English.
  - Item 60: More Action Needed To Stop Parking Violations, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    April 13. Item is in English.
  - Item 61: Limit On Hours of Work For Women Lifted, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    January 14. Item is in English.
  - Item 62: Two Appointed To Proposal Plan Committee, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    December 29. Item is in English.
  - Item 63: All Final Pay Checks To Be Mailed, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    February 4. Item is in English.
  - Item 64: Third Presentation of "Operation Second Chance", Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    February 12. Item is in English.
  - Item 65: Information About New Employment Program, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    May 29. Item is in English.
  - Item 66: Newspaper Story In Error, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    May 20. Item is in English.
  - Item 67: Pilot Program For Service To New Customers, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    April 25. Item is in English.
  - Item 68: Supervisors Asked To Forward Sales Prospect, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Item 69: Supervisors Asked To Assist On Downtown Survey, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    November 27. Item is in English.
  - Item 70: Two New members Appointed To Proposal Plan Committee, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Item 71: Cost of Living Allowance To Increase, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    February 24. Item is in English.
  - Item 72: Revised Income Tax Assistance Program, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    December 10. Item is in English.
  - Item 73: Company In New Research Program, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    December 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 74: 1969 Alex Dow Awards, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Item 75: Reminder: Holiday Weekend Exchange Discontinued Last Year, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    November 18. Item is in English.
  - Item 76: Action Steps Taken To Combine Overhead Lines and Underground Lines Into A Single Department, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    November 24. Item is in English.
  - Item 77: Cost-Of-Living Allowance To Increase, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Nnovember 25. Item is in English.
  - Item 78: Drug Abuse-New Problem For Supervision, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    May 14. Item is in English.
  - Item 79: Information About Downtown Detroit Redevlopment Plan, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    May 12. Item is in English.
  - Item 80: Dress and Discipline, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    May 8. Item is in English.
  - Item 81: Two New Members Appointed To Proposal Plan Committee, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    November 16. Item is in English.
  - Item 82: New Members Selected For Committee of Supervisors, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    November. Item is in English.
  - Item 83: Civil Rights Complaints-How They Are Processed and Guidelines For Supervisors, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    October 15. Item is in English.
  - Item 84: Arbitrator Upholds Company Position On Standards of Appearance, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    October 29. Item is in English.
  - Item 85: Computerized Personnel Data System To Be Installed, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    November 10. Item is in English.
  - Item 86: Picketing of General Offices Planned For Octobe 5, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    October 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 87: Emphasis is on Cost Reduction, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    October 13. Item is in English.
- Box: 7, folder: 2 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Run-Off Election To Be Held, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
    November 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: New Layout Shows Revised G.O. Area Parking Lot Arrangement, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Contributions Budget Reduced, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
    November 8. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Wage Adjustments Effective November 14, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
    November 17. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Many Unanswered Questions As Phase 2 Begins, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Regional Offices To Replace Local Customer Offices, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
    December 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Marketing Employes Vote Against Union In Run-Off Election, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Cost of Living Allowance to Increase, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Phase II - Update, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
    January 17. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Alcohol and Drug Misuse - The Supervisor's Role, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
    January 18. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Retroactive Wage Adjustments Approved, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
    January 26. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: President Meese Reports State of the Company, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
    January 24. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Paul W. MC Cracken Elected To Edison Board of Directors, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
    January 20. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Control of Costs, Better Scheduling, and More Reliable Operation-Targets of Our Project Management Organizations, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
    February 25. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Personnel Data System In Pilot Operation Prior to Company-Wide Use, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
    February 28. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Change In General Offices-Service Building Mail Procedure To Produce Savings and Improve Service, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Item 17: Retroactive Pay Adjustments To Be Paid, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
    February 22. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: New Tool To Help Supervisors Improve Attendance, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Item 19: Production Department and Security Department Lower Gate Operation Costs at Two Industrial Power Plants, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
    March 16. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Cost of Living Allowance To Increase, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
    March 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Interim Rate Increase Granted, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
    April 12. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Measurable Results Realized In New General Offices-Service Building Mail Procedure, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
    April 24. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Information About Distribution of Revised Employe Handbook Pages, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
    May 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Three New Members Appointed To Alex Dow Award Committee, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
    May 5. Item is in English.
- Box: 7, folder: 3 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Information Booklet of Purposes and Activities, Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Item is in English.
  - Item 2: e=mc^2, Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: General Order NO. 177, Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
    January 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: General Order No. 177, Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
    January 15. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: General Order No. 177, Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: General Order No. 177, Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: District Heating Service In Detroit, Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
    By E. E. Dubry. June. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: General Order No. 177, Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: The Detroit Edison Company Pertinent Company Data, Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Partners in Progress, Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Box: 7, folder: 4 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Information for New Employees, Publication (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Putting Human Relations Research To Work, Publication (Box 7, Folder 4)
    By Robert E. Schwab. December 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: A Guide For The Selection Of Supervisors, Publication (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: A Guide For The Selection Of Supervisors, Publication (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: hadbook For Edison People, Publication (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Hi There From The Folks At Detroit Edison!, Publication (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Information for New Employes, Publication (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: A cheerier place to work, Publication (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Box: 7, folder: 5 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Supplement To General Order NO. 203 (Promotions and Transfers, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: You Are The Company, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Detroit Edison engineering, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Inducting New Employees, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
    January. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Personnel Procedures, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: The Detroit Edison Company, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Application For Transfer, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Application For Employment, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Notice of Employment, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: Application For Employment, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: Follow-Up Report Employment Department, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
    March. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Veteran Follow-Up Report, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
    June. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Introduction Card, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Item 14: Instructions For Reporting, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Item 15: College Rating Card, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Item 16: Referred TO, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Item 17: Referred To, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Item 18: Fina Pay Request, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Item 19: Exit Interview, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Item 20: Your Job with Detroit Edison, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Item 21: General Order NO. 187 Employe Complaint Procedure, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Item 22: General Order NO. 207 Proposal Plan, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Item 23: General Order No. 232 Education Assitance, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
    September 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: General Order NO. 231 Management Development General Policy, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
    August 12. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: General Order NO. 203 Promotions and Transfers, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Item 26: Guide To Management Development, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
    December. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Some Facts About The Foundation For Economic Education, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Box: 7, folder: 6 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Supervisor Committee Reviews Employe Benefits, Publication (Box 7, Folder 6)
    May. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Hospital and Surgical Insurance For Employes and Their Families, Publication (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Announcing the New Group Life Insurance, Publication (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Employe Stock Purchase Plan, Publication (Box 7, Folder 6)
    August 10. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Planning For Tomorrow, Publication (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Planning for Tomorrow, Publication (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Box: 7, folder: 7 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Look Up Look Out For Wires, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Public Safety and Claims Prevention, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Rescue, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: George Washington didn't have electric wires to worrry about when he cut down his tree, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Spacemen play it Safe!, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Box: 7, folder: 8 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Absences and employee attitudes in an electric power company, Publication (Box 7, Folder 8)
    By Floyd Mann and Howard Baumgartel. December. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: College Graduate Development At Detroit Edison, Publication (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Planning for Supervisor Development, Publication (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Foreword, Publication (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Four Year Apprentice Lineman Training Schedule, Publication (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: Organization of the Marysville Job Training Program, Publication (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: Turbine Room Training Program, Publication (Box 7, Folder 8)
    By W. Ameel. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The supervisor's Concern With Costs in an electric power company, Publication (Box 7, Folder 8)
    By Floyd Mann and Howard Baumgartel. July. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Getting Better Proposals, Publication (Box 7, Folder 8)
    February. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Electric Power Systems and Nuclear Power, Publication (Box 7, Folder 8)
    By Walker L. Cisler. June 26. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Management Inventor and Development, Publication (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Box: 7, folder: 9 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: planning for Supervisor Development, Publication (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Preparting Today's Supervisor to meet Tomorrow's Problems, Publication (Box 7, Folder 9)
    By S. F. Leahy. September 13. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Job Description, Publication (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Management Inventory and Development, Publication (Box 7, Folder 9)
    June 11. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Report on th Trades and Operating Job Evaluation, Publication (Box 7, Folder 9)
    November 6. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Management Inventory and Development, Publication (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: To All Employes in A-grade Classifications, Publication (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: To All Employes in O- and T-grade classifications, Except Those Represented by a Union, Publication (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Item 9: Appraisals of Supervisors and Attitudes of their Employees in an Electric Power Company, Publication (Box 7, Folder 9)
    By Floyd Mann and James Dent. March. Item is in English.
- Box: 7, folder: 10 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Putting Your Ideas to Work, Publication (Box 7, Folder 10)
    December 7. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Supervising our Employe Proposal Plan, Publication (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Box: 7, folder: 11 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Press Pact Near In Detroit Strike, Publication (Box 7, Folder 11)
    January 12. Item is in English.
- Box: 7, folder: 12 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Employees' Retirement Plan For Michigan banks, Publication (Box 7, Folder 12)
    April 30. Item is in English.
- Box: 7, folder: 13 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Assessment & Development, Publication (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: Assessment & Development, Publication (Box 7, Folder 13)
    October. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Assessment & Development, Publication (Box 7, Folder 13)
    April. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Assessment & Development, Publication (Box 7, Folder 13)
    August. Item is in English.
- Box: 7, folder: 14 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Assessment & Development, Publication (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Box: 7, folder: 15 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: The Road to Change Some Pages from Experience in the Practical Art of Getting Things Done, Publication (Box 7, Folder 15)
    By David E. Lilienthal. Item is in English.
- Box: 7, folder: 16 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Successful College Recruiting This Year, Publication (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: Working together at Diamond Alkali, Publication (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: Personnel Directory, Publication (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Item 4: Have You Considered Diamond In Your Future?, Publication (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Item 5: Consider Diamond in your future, Publication (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Box: 7, folder: 17 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: the story of Diamond Chemicals, Publication (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: Chemicals You Live By, Publication (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: the Diamond Story, Publication (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: Annual Reprot to the stockholders of Diamond Alkali Company and subsidiary companies for the year ended December 31, 1958, Publication (Box 7, Folder 17)
    March 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Diamond Story, Publication (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Item 6: The Diamond Story, Publication (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Item 7: Diamond Story, Publication (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Box: 7, folder: 18 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Shareholders Aprove Diamon, Shamrock Merger, Publication (Box 7, Folder 18)
    November 30. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Diamond Shamrock Merger, Publication (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: Background Information, Publication (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: Diamond Alkali Company Annual Report 1963, Publication (Box 7, Folder 18)
    March 2. Item is in English.
- Box: 7, folder: 19 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Selected Reading On Manpower Development, Publication (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Box: 7, folder: 20 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Educational Gift Matching Program, Publication (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Item 2: Diamond Alkali Company is pleased to announce, Publication (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Item 3: Four-Fold Program of Aid to Education, Publication (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Item 4: Tuition Refund Quarterly Report, Publication (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Box: 9, folder: 1 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Sales Training Programs, Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: The Supervisor's Manpower Development Guide, Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Box: 9, folder: 2 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Plant Rules and Safety Instructions, Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Box: 9, folder: 3 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Orientation Program For financial personnel, Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Orientation Program For Technical Personnel, Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Box: 9, folder: 4 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Job Description Outline, Publication (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Accounting Graudates, Publication (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Sales and Marketing Opportunities, Publication (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Plastics Orientation Program, Publication (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Engineering and Chemistry Graduates, Publication (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Box: 9, folder: 5 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Agreement between Diamond Shoe Corporation and Marlborough Shoe Workers Associates, Inc., Publication (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Box: 9, folder: 6 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Group Insurance Plan For Employees and Their Dependents, Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Box: 9, folder: 7 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Personnel Record, Publication (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Application for Employment, Publication (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Box: 9, folder: 8 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Management Organization, Publication (Box 9, Folder 8)
    October 1. Item is in English.
- Box: 9, folder: 9 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Group Insurance Program For Our Executive, Sales, Clerical Employees, Publication (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Box: 9, folder: 10 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Retirement Plan For Employees Of Ditto, Incorporated, The Ditto Press, Incorporated Lincoln Paper Company, Publication (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Box: 9, folder: 11 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: By-Laws Dodge Mutual Relief Association, Publication (Box 9, Folder 11)